Did you know, creating your product photos and videos?
Inside Amazon's AI Studio is now possible
within minutes.
Let me show you how I use Amazon's AI tools to create pictures and videos for
my brand.
I'm Pallavi Pande, owner at Dtocs.
At Dtocs we make sustainable tableware like your plates
and bowls out of palm leaves and bamboo fiber.
As a small brand with limited resources and budget,
creating professional videos and photographs used to be expensive.
But now Amazon's creative tools
make it easier.
Amazon's AI Video Generator turns one single product image into videos automatically.
These AI creative tools were designed for small businesses to develop professional advertising
content without the help of agencies or studios.
It took few seconds but it generated the
image.
You go into products and add your product ASIN right here on the tab, click on generate.
I'll show you the results.
So if you're an Amazon seller or product brand, AI tools like this help us create high quality
content quickly.